jabil.com 2005-12-30

# Policy

---|---|---|---|---|---  
|   
|  | 

Privacy Policy

>   
> Safe Harbor and Online Users Privacy Policy  
> Jabil Circuit, Inc.
> 
> 1. Purpose.  Jabil Circuit, Inc. has created the following Privacy Policy (a) to comply with the United States Safe Harbor, (b) to facilitate the exchange of information between Jabil Circuit, Inc.'s offices located in the United States, in the European Union, and in other jurisdictions, and (c) to govern information Jabil Circuit, Inc. generally receives through this Web Site.  The scope and terms of this Privacy Policy are set out below. 
> 
> 2. Your Agreement.  Your use of this Web Site, or submission of information via this Web Site, constitutes your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  Please review these terms to ensure they are acceptable.  In addition, please also review our Terms of Use, located at <http://jabil.com/legal.asp> to ensure they are similarly acceptable. 
> 
> 3. Definitions.  Capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have the meanings set forth in Section 21 (Defined Terms).
> 
> 4. Safe Harbor Certification.  Jabil US has adopted (i) this Safe Harbor and Online Users Privacy Policy and (ii) a separate Jabil US EU Employee Privacy Policy in order to participate in the US Safe Harbor.  Jabil US certifies with the U.S. Department of Commerce that these Privacy Policies comply with the Safe Harbor and provide the adequate protections specified in the Data Protection Directive. 
> 
> 5. Scope of Privacy Policy.    
> 5.1. Application to Jabil US and Jabil Affiliates in the US.  This Privacy Policy governs Personal Data Collection Practices of Jabil US with respect to Personal Data that Jabil US and US Affiliates receive from Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other data subjects.   
> ****5.2.  No Application to Jabil Employees; Employee Personal Data Protection.** ** This Privacy Policy does not set out the Personal Data Protection Practices of Jabil US and Jabil Affiliates with respect to Jabil Employees, and this Privacy Policy does not cover Jabil Employees. 
> 
> 6. Site Visitors.  Information which Jabil US may receive concerning Site Visitors using the Jabil Web Site falls into two broad categories: Aggregate Information (defined below in Section 6.1) and Personal Data.  This Section sets out the Personal Data Protection Practices applicable to Site Visitors.    
> 6.1. Aggregate Information from Site Visitors.  "Aggregate Information" is information that does not identify a Site Visitor, and may include, for example, statistical information concerning the web pages on the Jabil Web Site that users most frequent.  Aggregate Information may be collected through cookies and similar Internet technologies. "Cookies" are small text files that a web site can use to recognize repeat users, to facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site, and to compile aggregate data to improve the web site and focus advertising.  If Jabil US uses cookies or other similar Internet technologies on the Jabil Web Site, these technologies will not collect or retain the Site Visitor's name or other Personal Data.  In addition, no third parties are permitted to use for their own purposes cookies Jabil US may create at the Jabil Web Site.  With Aggregate Information, Jabil US may undertake or commission statistical and other summary analyses of Site Visitor behavior and characteristics when visiting the Jabil Web Site. Although Jabil US may share this aggregate information with third parties, no aggregate information Jabil US provides to third parties will allow such third parties to identify a Site Visitor, or determine anything personal about the Site Visitor.  
> 6.2. Personal Data from Site Visitors.  Jabil US may receive Personal Data from Site Visitors who use the Jabil Web Site, where applicable, (i) to submit questions or comments to Jabil US, (ii) to request information about products or services offered by Jabil US or Jabil Affiliates, or (iii) to employ other features that may be available at the Web Site which call for submission of Personal Data.  Jabil US uses Personal Data which Site Visitors submit through the Jabil Web Site (a) to respond to the Site Visitor (although Jabil US in this Privacy Policy undertakes no obligation to respond to any Site Visitor), and (b) to provide the services or products requested by the Site Visitor, where the requested services or products are, in fact, offered by Jabil US and are in accordance with Jabil US's standard business procedures.    
> 6.2.1. Further Uses.  Jabil US and US Affiliates may wish to use a Site Visitor's Personal Information for purposes which are in addition to those specified in Section 6.2 (Personal Data from Site Visitors) and which do not involve disclosures beyond those permitted in Section 12 (Onward Disclosures).  If Jabil US uses a Site Visitor's Personal Data for these additional Jabil-related purposes, such as for contacting the Site Visitor independent of an inquiry from the Site Visitor, the Site Visitor shall be entitled to opt-out of such additional uses in accordance with Section 11 (Choice and Opt-Out Rights).    
> 6.2.2. Disclosure.  Jabil US will not disclose Personal Data received from Site Visitors except in accordance with Section 12 (Onward Disclosures).
> 
> 7. Employment Applicants.  The Jabil Web Site allows Employment Applicants to submit employment applications to Jabil US and to Jabil Affiliates.  In addition, Jabil US and US Affiliates may receive  from EU Affiliates information concerning EU Employment Applicants.  Applications submitted by Employment Applicants will include Personal Data.  This Section provides Jabil US's Personal Data Protection Practices with respect to such Personal Data.   
> 7.1. Use of Employment Applicants' Personal Data.  Jabil US uses Personal Data it receives from Employment Applicants (i) to process the Applicants' applications, (ii) to contact references which may be identified in such applications, (iii) to collect and compile additional information concerning the Applicant from available sources, consistent with applicable law, and (iv) to evaluate the Employment Applicant's candidacy for employment.    
> 7.1.1. Further Uses.  Jabil US and US Affiliates may wish to use an Employment Applicant's Personal Data for purposes which are in addition to those specified in Section 7.1 (Use of Employment Applicant's Personal Data) and which do not involve disclosures beyond those permitted in Section 12 (Onward Disclosures).  If Jabil US uses an Employment Applicant's Personal Data for these additional Jabil-related purposes, such as for contacting the Employment Applicant independent of the employment application process, the Employment Applicant shall be entitled to opt-out of such additional uses in accordance with Section 11 (Choice and Opt-Out Rights).    
> 7.1.2. Disclosure.  Jabil US will not disclose Personal Data received from an Employment Applicant except in accordance with Section 12 (Onward Disclosures).  If the Employment Applicant seeks employment with a Jabil Affiliate, Jabil US will provide relevant information concerning the Employment Applicant, including Personal Data, to such Jabil Affiliate, subject to Section 12 (Onward Disclosures).     
> **7.2.  Sensitive Data**.  Jabil US and Jabil Affiliates do not request Sensitive Data from Employment Applicants, except as expressly permitted under the local laws and regulations of the applicable jurisdiction.  In the event an Employment Applicant submits Sensitive Data, Jabil US will handle such Sensitive Data in accordance with Section 10 (Sensitive Data). 7.3. No Obligation to Consider Application.  Due to the nature of the Internet and the structure of the Jabil Web Site, Jabil US may receive (i) substantially more applications through the Jabil Web Site than Jabil US wishes to review, (ii) applications which do not meet the requirements for positions that are available, and (iii) applications at points where no positions are currently available. Accordingly, there is no assurance that Jabil US will process or review materials which Employment Applicants submit seeking employment with Jabil US or any of its Affiliates, and Jabil US expressly disclaims any obligation to engage in such processing or review, and disclaims any obligation to respond to any Employment Applicant submissions.
> 
> 8. EU Business Contacts.  Jabil US may receive or collect Personal Data with respect to EU Business Contacts, directly or through an EU Affiliate.    
> 8.1. Use of Personal Data from EU Business Contacts.  Jabil US uses Personal Data from EU Business Contacts (i) to perform and enforce applicable contractual obligations with an EU Business Contact, (ii) to evaluate an existing or prospective relationship with such EU Business Contact, including a possible merger or acquisition, (iii) to perform services or provide goods requested by the EU Business Contract; and (iv) to solicit business from or present business opportunities to the EU Business Contact.    
> 8.2. Disclosure.  Jabil US will not disclose Personal Data received from EU Business Contacts except in accordance with Section 12 (Onward Disclosures).    
> 8.3. Business Card Information.  Business Card Information (as defined below) is customarily freely exchanged, and generally does not qualify as Personal Data because it is publicly available, as set out in Section 21.15.  Accordingly, Business Card Information is treated differently than Personal Data under this Privacy Policy, as set out below:    
> 8.3.1. Business Card Information.  Except in the case of merger or acquisition candidates and in other circumstances where additional information is advisable, in its uses of information from EU Business Contacts Jabil US and US Affiliates generally employ only that Personal Data (i) which identifies individual decision-makers at the relevant EU Business Contact, and (ii) which consists of such individual's business address, business email, and business telephone number (collectively "Business Card Information").    
> 8.3.2. Disclosing Business Card Information In Connection With Third Party Business Opportunities.  Jabil US and US Affiliates provide Business Card Information from EU Business Contracts to unaffiliated third parties where Jabil US and US Affiliates believe a business opportunity or other relevant opportunity is presented.
> 
>   9. EU Consumers.  Jabil US may receive from its EU Affiliates Personal Data concerning EU Consumers.  If Jabil US obtains Personal Data from EU Consumers, Jabil US shall use such Personal Data (i) to assist the EU Affiliate in providing goods and services to EU Consumers, and (ii) to respond to inquiries from EU Consumers.    
> 9.1. Further Uses.  Jabil US and US Affiliates may wish to use an EU Consumer's Personal Information for purposes which are in addition to those specified in this Section 9 (EU Consumers) and which do not involve disclosures beyond those permitted in Section 12 (Onward Disclosures).  If Jabil US uses an EU Consumer's Personal Data for these additional Jabil-related purposes, such as for contacting the EU Consumer independent of an inquiry from the EU Consumer, the EU Consumer shall be entitled to opt-out of such additional uses in accordance with Section 11 (Choice and Opt-Out Rights).    
> 9.2. Disclosure.  Jabil US will not disclose Personal Data it receives from EU Consumers except in accordance with Section 12 (Onward Disclosures).
> 
> 10. Sensitive Data.  This Section provides Jabil US's and US Affiliates' Personal Data Protection Practices regarding Sensitive Data.    
> 10.1. Compliance with Law.  Jabil US and Jabil Affiliates comply with laws and regulations applicable to Sensitive Data in their respective jurisdictions, and do not collect or request Sensitive Data except in accordance with such laws and regulations.    
> 10.2. Additional Protections for Sensitive Data.  If Jabil US or US Affiliates receive Sensitive Data concerning an EU Data Subject, Jabil US and US Affiliates will not disclose such Sensitive Data to any third party and will not use the Sensitive Data for any purpose other than (i) for the purpose for which it was originally provided by the EU Data Subject or (ii) for a later purpose expressly authorized or consented to by the EU Data Subject, except as provided below in Section 10.3 (Exception from Consent Requirement for Certain Disclosures).    
> 10.3. Exception from Consent Requirement for Certain Disclosures.  In accordance with the Data Protection Directive, and notwithstanding the requirements of Section 10.2 (Additional Protections for Sensitive Data), Jabil US and US Affiliates shall be entitled to use or disclose Sensitive Data (as well as Personal Data) where such disclosure or use: (i) is in the vital interests of the Data Subject or another person, (ii) is necessary for the establishment of legal claims or defenses, (iii) is required to provide medical care or diagnosis, (iv) is necessary to carry out Jabil US's or a Jabil Affiliate's obligations in the field of employment law, or (v) is related to data manifestly made public by the Data Subject.
> 
> 11. Choice and Opt-Out Rights.  Jabil US and US Affiliates will use the Personal Data of a Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subject for the purposes specified in Section 6 (Site Visitors), Section 7 (Employment Applicants), Section 8 (EU Business Contacts), and Section 9 (EU Consumers), above (collectively, "Original Purposes").  Jabil US or US Affiliates may wish periodically to use such Personal Data for purposes other than the Original Purposes, including for purposes of providing the Data Subjects with direct marketing and other information.  Information provided to a Data Subject for such purposes is referred to collectively as "Direct Marketing Information."    
> 11.1. Opt-Out Notice.  If a Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subject does not want to receive Direct Marketing Information from Jabil US, the Data Subject shall complete and execute the attached Opt Out Notice for Direct Marketing and mail it to Jabil US at the address indicated on the notice.    
> 11.2. Response.  If Jabil US receives an Opt Out Notice for Direct Marketing from a Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subject, Jabil US and US Affiliates will restrict their uses of the Data Subject's Personal Data to the Original Purposes, or such other purposes as the Data Subject may authorize, subject to the Data Subject's rights under Section 14 (Rights to Access, Change, or Delete Personal Data).  Jabil US shall be entitled to a reasonable period of time to process a Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subject's request under this Section 11 (Choice and Opt-Out Rights).
> 
> 12. Onward Disclosures.  Jabil US discloses Personal Data of Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects only to its employees who have a reasonable "need to know" such Personal Data, and such employees are under obligations of confidentiality to Jabil US.  Jabil US will not disclose the Personal Data of Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects to anyone other than such reasonable "need to know" employees, except as provided below in this Section 12 (Onward Disclosures), in Section 8.3.2 (Disclosing Business Card Information In Connection With Third Party Business Opportunities), and in Section 18 (Assignment).  
> 12.1. US Affiliates.  Jabil US requires each US Affiliate to comply with this Privacy Policy, and Jabil US's Safe Harbor certification is designed to include US Affiliates.  Accordingly, Personal Data covered by this Privacy Policy is disclosed to US Affiliates, subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  Similar to Jabil US, a US Affiliate discloses Personal Data of Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects only to those of its employees who have a reasonable "need to know" such Personal Data, and such employees are under obligations of confidentiality to the applicable US Affiliate.  US Affiliates will not disclose the Personal Data of Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects to anyone other than such reasonable "need to know" employees, except as provided below in this Section 12 (Onward Disclosures), in Section 8.3.2 (Disclosing Business Card Information In Connection With Third Party Business Opportunities), and in Section 18 (Assignment).  
> 12.2. Jabil Agents.  Jabil US and US Affiliates may disclose Personal Data of Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects (i) to a third party that is acting as Jabil US's agent to perform tasks on Jabil US's behalf and under Jabil US's supervision, including but not limited to its Worldwide Affiliates, and (ii) to a third party that is acting as a US Affiliate's agent to perform tasks on the Affiliate's behalf and under its supervision, including but not limited to its Worldwide Affiliates, provided the third party either (a) subscribes to the Safe Harbor principles or is subject to the Data Protection Directive or another personal data protection adequacy finding of the EU or (b) agrees (1) to provide auditable protections for the Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subject's privacy interests that are no less protective than those set out in this Privacy Policy, and (2) to use the Personal Data only for the purposes for which the third party has been engaged by Jabil US or the US Affiliate.  
> 12.3. Other Third Parties.  Except as provided in Section 10.3 (Exception for Consent Requirement for Certain Disclosures), Jabil US and US Affiliates will not disclose Personal Data of Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects to any third party other than one identified in this Section 12 (Onward Disclosures) without the express consent of the Data Subject. 
> 
> 13. Confidentiality and Security Of Personal Data.    Jabil US and US Affiliates maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to secure Personal Data of Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects, and to prevent unauthorized access.  These technical security systems are structured to deter and prevent hackers and others from accessing Personal Data of Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects.    
> 13.1. Limitations on Technical Protections.  Due to evolving technologies, Jabil US and US Affiliates cannot provide assurance that Personal Data provided will remain free from loss, misuse, or alteration through third parties who, despite Jabil US's efforts, obtain unauthorized access.    
> 13.2. Employee Education.  Employees of Jabil US and US Affiliates with access to Personal Data concerning Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects are educated concerning Jabil's applicable Personal Data Protection Practices, and employees who violate these Practices are subject to disciplinary process. 
> 
> 14. Right To Access, Change, or Delete Personal Data.  Upon reasonable request (with the term "reasonable" to be interpreted in accordance with FAQ 8 of the Safe Harbor), and to the extent the request does not compromise its Personal Data Protection Practices, Jabil US allows Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects access to their Personal Data to correct, amend or delete such Data.    
> 14.1. Requests.  All requests under this Section 14 (Right to Access, Change, or Delete Personal Data) must be sent in writing to the address specified below in Section 20 (Complaints, Questions, and Requests).    
> 14.2. Timing of Response.  Jabil US endeavors to timely respond to proper requests for access and changes or deletions under this under this Section 14 (Right to Access, Change, or Delete Personal Data).  Any questions or inquiries concerning the timing of Jabil US's response should be directed to the address specified below in Section 20 (Complaints, Questions, and Requests).    
> 14.3. Conditions.  Jabil US reserves (i) the right, where permitted by law or other legal authority, to charge a reasonable fee to cover the costs incurred in responding to an appropriate request, and (ii) reserves the right to delete such information (and certify to the Data Subject such deletion), rather than correct or update this information where the information retains limited utility.    
> 14.4. Extent of Data Deletions.  Upon fulfilling a requested deletion of Personal Data under this Section 14 (Right to Access, Change, or Delete Personal Data), Jabil US and US Affiliates will cease to use such Data and will use commercially reasonable efforts to remove all record of such Data; however, it may be impossible to delete the information completely from applicable Jabil databases, due to backups and records of deletions.
> 
> 15. Privacy Protection For Children.  The Jabil Web Site is not directed at children, and Jabil US will not accept or request Personal Data from individuals Jabil US knows to be under 13.  In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, if Jabil US learns that a child under 13 has provided Personal Data, Jabil US will delete this information from its databases, in accordance with its deletion policy, set out in Section 14 (Right to Access, Change, or Delete Personal Data). For more information regarding a child under the age of 13 providing personal information to a web site, see the Federal Trade Commission's web site explaining the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 at <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/>.
> 
> 16. Exceptions.  As further provided in Section 10.3 (Exception for Consent Requirement for Certain Disclosures), Jabil US and US Affiliates may disclose Personal Data as may be required in legal proceedings, or in response to a subpoena, court order, or administrative order compelling disclosure.  In addition, in cases involving a threat of imminent harm to a Data Subject or to others, Jabil US and US Affiliates may release such Personal Data to prevent or mitigate the threat.  In any such case, Jabil US and US Affiliates will seek to limit the scope of disclosure, and will disclose only such Data as is reasonably required to fulfill the purpose of the disclosure. 
> 
> 17. Changes to This Privacy Policy.  The Personal Data Protection Practices defined in this Privacy Policy are current as of December 2003.  Jabil US reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time consistent with applicable privacy laws and principles.  Unless such changes afford greater protections to the privacy interests of Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects, such changes will apply only to Personal Data received after the effective date of such change.  Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects should refer to this Privacy Policy for information concerning such changes.  Where Jabil US deems appropriate, other forms of notice will be given concerning such changes.  
>   
> 18. Assignment.  Jabil US and US Affiliates shall be entitled to assign or transfer to a third party Personal Data that Jabil US receives under this Privacy Policy, in connection with the sale or transfer of all or an applicable portion of its business or assets or those of a US Affiliate; provided such third party agrees before receipt of such Data to comply with restrictions on the use of such Data that are no less protective of the privacy interests of Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects than those set out in this Privacy Policy. 
> 
> 19. Choice Of Law And Jurisdiction.  This Privacy Policy shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Florida, without regard to any conflict of law provisions.  Any dispute arising under this Privacy Policy shall be resolved exclusively by the state or federal courts sitting in Pinellas County, Florida, with the exception of those disputes for which the Data Protection Directive requires resolution in an alternative forum or jurisdiction. 
> 
> 20. Complaints, Questions, and Requests.  Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subjects may contact Jabil US and US Affiliates (i) with complaints concerning this Privacy Policy or its implementation, (ii) with questions concerning this Policy, and (iii) with requests under Section 14 (Right to Access, Change, or Delete Personal Data), at the following address:
> 
> Jabil Circuit, Inc.  
> US Safe Harbor Compliance  
> C/O Heather Mourtakos  
> 10560 Dr. Martin Luther King Street North  
> St. Petersburg, FL  33716  
> Phone:  727-803-3219  
> Fax:  727-203-3219   
> e-mail: [ussafeharborcompliance@jabil.com](mailto:ussafeharborcompliance@jabil.com)
> 
> 21.  ** _Defined Terms_**.  Capitalized terms in this Privacy Policy have the following meaning:
> 
> 21.1. "Business Card Information" means the information found on a standard business card, as further defined in Section 8.3.1 (Business Card Information), below. 
> 
> 21.2. "Data Subject" means the natural person who is the subject of, and identified in, Personal Data. 
> 
> 21.3. "Direct Marketing Information" has the meaning set out in Section 11 (Choice and Opt-Out Rights). 
> 
> 21.4. "Employment Applicant" means an individual who submits an application for employment with Jabil US or a Jabil Affiliate through the Jabil Web Site.  In the case of applicants who are located in the EU and whose privacy interests are protected under the Data Protection Directive, the term "Employment Applicant" shall also include applicants who submit applications through any medium, including the Jabil Web Site.
> 
> 21.5. "European Union" or "EU" means the European Union consisting of its Member States, covered by the European Union Data Protection Directive.
> 
> 21.6. "European Union Data Protection Directive" or "Data Protection Directive" means the directive of the European Parliament and Council of October 24, 1995 that governs the processing of personal information within and without the European Union, the movement of such information, and the promulgation of national legislation of European Union member states consistent with this Directive.  For more information on the European Union Data Protection Directive, please see <http://europa.eu.int/comm/internal_market/en> /dataprot/index.htm.
> 
> 21.7. "EU Affiliate" means a Jabil Affiliate located in the European Union and subject to the Data Protection Directive. 
> 
> 21.8. "EU Business Contact" means a commercial or non-profit organization which is located in the European Union and covered by the Data Protection Directive other than an EU Affiliate.  The term "EU Business Contact" includes (i) vendors and service providers to, and commercial customers of Jabil US or Jabil Affiliates; (ii) organizations which may be candidates for merger with or acquisition by Jabil US or Jabil Affiliates, or (iii) the individual employees, shareholders, owners, and agents of such EU Business Contacts, to the extent these individuals' privacy interests are protected under the Data Protection Directive. 
> 
> 21.9. "EU Consumer" means a consumer purchaser or consumer user of the products or services of Jabil US or Jabil Affiliates who is located in the European Union and whose privacy interests are protected under the Data Protection Directive
> 
> 21.10. "EU Data Subject" means a Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subject who is located in the European Union and whose privacy interests are protected under the Data Protection Directive.
> 
> 21.11. "Jabil Affiliate" means any corporation, partnership, limited liability company or other entity directly or indirectly controlled by or under the common control of Jabil Circuit, Inc.  By way of clarifying example and not by way of limitation, the term "Jabil Affiliate" includes those entities and plants identified at <http://www.jabil.com/419.asp>
> 
> 21.12. "Jabil Employee" means an employee of Jabil US or a Jabil Affiliate.
> 
> 21.13. "Jabil US" means Jabil Circuit, Inc. incorporated under the laws of the state of Delaware having its corporate headquarters in St. Petersburg, Florida, USA. 
> 
> 21.14. "Jabil Web Site" or the"Web Site" means Jabil US's Internet web site located at [www.jabil.com](http://www.jabil.com/).
> 
> 21.15. "Personal Data" means data that personally identifies a Data Subject or that may be used to personally identify a Data Subject (such as an identification number that identifies a Data Subject).  Personal Data includes data such as an individual's name, address, phone number, email address, user ID and password, personal billing information, and credit card information.  Personal Data does not include data that is encoded or anonymized, or publicly available information that has not been combined with non-public Personal Data.  This Privacy Policy imposes greater restrictions on Sensitive Data (as this term is defined below) than on Personal Data; accordingly, unless expressly stated, the term "Personal Data" does not include "Sensitive Data." 
> 
> 21.16. "Personal Data Protection Practices" means practices concerning the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Data. 
> 
> 21.17. "Safe Harbor" means the program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission, which enables U.S. companies to satisfy the requirements of the European Union Data Protection Directive.  For more information on the United States Safe Harbor, please see <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.
> 
> 21.18. "Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subject" means EU Business Contacts, EU Consumers, Employment Applicants, or Site Visitors.  The term "Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subject" does not include any other person or Data Subject, and does not include Jabil Employees, as further set out in Section 5.2 (No Application to Jabil Employees).    
> 21.19. "Sensitive Data" means Personal Data that discloses a Data Subject's medical or health condition; race or ethnicity; political, religious or philosophical affiliations or opinions; sexual orientation; or trade union membership. 
> 
> 21.20. "Site Visitor" means a person who browses the Jabil Web Site or submits information to Jabil US through the Jabil Web Site.  For purposes of clarity, the term "Site Visitor" does not include Employment Applicants.    
>   
> 21.21. "US Affiliate" means a Jabil Affiliate located in the United States. 
> 
> 21.22. "Worldwide Affiliates" means Jabil Affiliates other than (i) EU Affiliates or (ii) US Affiliates. 
> 
>   
> Opt Out Notice For Direct Marketing
> 
> Capitalized terms in this Notice are defined in   
> Jabil US's Privacy Policy for Safe Harbor and Online Users.    
> This Policy is located at [www.jabil.com](http://www.jabil.com/)
> 
> Jabil US and US Affiliates periodically may wish to use Personal Data to send Direct Marketing Information to a Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subject.  Such Data Subjects have the right to opt out of receiving such Direct Marketing Information, in accordance with Section 11 of Jabil US's Privacy Policy for Safe Harbor and Online Users.  If you are a Safe Harbor and Online Privacy Policy Data Subject, and you choose to exercise this opt out right, please complete and execute this form and mail it to Jabil US at the following address: 
> 
> Jabil Circuit, Inc.  
> US Safe Harbor Compliance  
> C/O Heather Mourtakos  
> 10560 Dr. Martin Luther King Street North  
> St. Petersburg, FL  33716
> 
> __________________________________________
> 
> I HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND JABIL CIRCUIT, INC.'S. PRIVACY POLICY FOR SAFE HARBOR AND ONLINE USERS AND HEREBY EXERCISE MY RIGHT UNDER APPLICABLE PRIVACY LAWS AND PRINCIPLES TO OPT OUT OF JABIL CIRCUIT, INC.'S USE OF MY PERSONAL DATA FOR ITS DIRECT MARKETING PURPOSES (AS THOSE TERMS ARE DEFINED IN THE JABIL PRIVACY POLICY FOR SAFE HARBOR AND ONLINE USERS, LOCATED AT [WWW.JABIL.COM](http://www.jabil.com/))  BY DOING SO, I, AS THE DATA SUBJECT, UNDERSTAND THAT JABIL CIRCUIT, INC. WILL NOT SEND ME DIRECT MARKETING INFORMATION, BUT MAY STILL USE MY PERSONAL DATA FOR THE PURPOSE IT WAS ORIGINALLY COLLECTED OR FOR WHICH I SUBSEQUENTLY AUTHORIZE AND MAY STILL DISCLOSE MY PERSONAL DATA, AS DESCRIBED ELSEWHERE IN THE PRIVACY POLICY AND AS PERMITTED UNDER OR REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW.
> 
>   
> Signed:___________________________________  
> Print Name:________________________________  
> Date:_____________________________________   
> Mailing Address:____________________________  
> Telephone No.:______________________________
> 
> FCH1 #79169 v1  
> 

|  |  |  |   
|  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
Terms | Privacy © 2004 Jabil Circuit    
  
|  |
